so scrolls are the bad guys
and you're free
a race of noble lawyers heroes noble
warrior heroes
[Music]
your life began the day it nearly ended
we found you with no memory we made you
one of us so you could live longer
stronger superior
you were reborn
I keep having these
memories something in my past is the key
to all of this
you're not a flatus thing you see that's
a yes or no question yes
[Music]
would you like to know
what you really are
I think I had a life here
what aren't you telling me
you've come a long way the universe
strong as you think
the slaw is just the beginning
I'm not going to fight your war
[Music]
I'm gonna end it
I'm super cute as lovely aren't you
what's your name Jerry's hmm